

# **ABOUT ME**

As a double -degree student entering the final years of university with some limitations in experience, I have a desire to apply the knowledge I have learned from books into a professional working environment, receive specialist competence or future career orientation and access to sources of legal knowledge and in-depth study materials in the legal field. On that basis, I will strive to become an official member, contributing to the success of your company. In the long term, after graduating from school, completing C1 Advanced exam and legal practicing certificate; I aim to become a professional legal officer and have the opportunity to try many fields, different products and countries contribute to social change.

## CONTACT

+84 372207946

nchauanh9999@gmail.com

No 136, 63 lane, Le Duc Tho street,
Nam Tu Liem dictrict, Ha Noi

## SKILLS

01. COMMUNICATION

**02. TEAMWORK** 

03. MS OFFICE (WORD, EXCEL,

POWERPOINT, CANVA)

04. RESEARCH

05. HARD-WORKING

**AND WRITING SKILLS** 

06. ENGLISH: SPEAKING

# NGUYĒN CHÂU ANH

**LEGAL INTERN** 

# **EDUCATION**

LAM SON HIGH SCHOOL FOR THE 2017- 2020 GIFTED

**SPECIALIZE IN HISTORY** 

VNU SCHOOL OF LAW

2020- PRESENT

JUNIOR/ MAJOR IN INTERNATIONAL TRADE LAW

VNU UNIVERSITY OF LANGUAGE AND INTERNATIONAL STUDIES

2021- PRESENT

SOPHOMORE / DEPARTMENT OF ENGLISH LANGUAGE AND CULTURAL

## WORK EXPERIENCE

**CLASS MANAGER** 

1/2022-8/2022

#### MIND X TECHNOLOGY SCHOOL

Learn how to use classin, Ims software to facilitate classroom management. Allocating time properly and patience is also very important for multitasks such as: support teachers in managing class and clarifying instructions, take care of students throughout study.

CUSTOMER SERVICES

3/2022-6/2022

#### ALPHA FURNITURE JOINT STOCK COMPANY

Aquire basic knowledge about telesale: communication skills, handling situations and providing information about furniture products to customers over the phone, answering customers' questions about interior quality via email and zalo, contact the warranty team to promptly repair damaged devices.

**ENGLISH TEACHING ASSISTANT** 

6/2022-8/2022

#### **HOAN ENGLISH CLASS**

Improve knowledge transfer skills, flexibility, and high initiative by making lesson plans suitable for difference levels before class, supplementing basic knowledge for inferior students in the elementary curriculum.